weeklywomen.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy – Weekly Women

By using Weekly Women, you are bound by and agree to the terms of the privacy policy that is detailed below. Please refrain from using Weekly Women if you are opposed to these terms.

**Collected Information and Its Use  **

Personal information collected through Weekly Women is limited only to the purposes described below. If any personal information will be used in a way other than intended, you will be asked for your consent.

Regarding Your Account Information: In order to give users the best experience possible, Weekly Women asks for and records personal information, including your email address and name, if you login through your Facebook account.

Submissions from Users: To provide the fullest version of Weekly Women’s services, your submissions may be stored or publicly displayed on Weekly Women. Submissions will be combined with the first and last name and the photo associated with your Facebook account. If you wish to change these details, you can do so on your account page. Any information posted to Weekly Women, including reviews, ratings of businesses or any information displayed through your account profile are referred to as “Submissions.”

Weekly Women Feedback: Personal information, such as information provided in your communication with Weekly Women when you provide feedback to us, ask a question or register a complaint will be recorded in order for us to effectively and efficiently respond to questions.

User Activity: In order for Weekly Women to provide the best possible service to our users, information such as your browser type, IP address, searches, timestamp information and the pages you view is recorded. We use this information for statistical analyses of site interaction, allowing us the ability to see what areas of Weekly Women are being used the most. This information cannot identify you.

Cookie Usage: Cookies, or small pieces of information that are sent to your hard drive while viewing the site, are used to help us improve the quality of service by assisting us in identifying your browser. Weekly Women may utilize both persistent cookies, which stay on your computer until they are deleted and session cookies, which expire when you close your browser. While you can disable the use of cookies through your browser, you may limit the functionality of some areas of Weekly Women.

Enforcement of Term of Service and Privacy Policy: Any information, including personal information, that is collected during your use of Weekly Women may be used for enforcement or investigation of our privacy policy or terms of service.

**Transfer of Information**

As indicated in our terms of service, third parties may receive your submissions, which in turn may be published or displayed publicly through their websites or other platforms. Information included with submissions distributed to third parties includes our account name. However, your personal information is not included, unless listed in your submission.

Your information may be shared with third parties in order for us to provide a number of services, including customer support, quality assurance testing, account creation and synchronization of your contacts with other software applications. These third parties may not use this personal information for any other purposes than what you request.

Affiliates, such as our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures or companies under common control, that are with us now or in the future may have access to your personal information. These affiliates must honor this privacy policy. If another company obtains the assets to our company, your personal information will then be possessed by that company. However, that company will also obtain the obligations and rights detailed in this privacy policy.

If it is deemed necessary to enforce our privacy policy or terms of service, protect the rights or reputation of Weekly Women or its users, affiliates or public, comply with any legal processes, such as warrants, subpoenas, statutes or court orders or to take action again suspected illegal activity, personal information may be given to third parties. Weekly Women is not required to question or contest the validity of any governmental request.

In connection with an actual or prospective business partnership with third parties, including advertisers and distributors, information that relates to user behavior may be disclosed. Information such as the number of users that have seen or clicked advertising banners is what would be disclosed.

Advertisements served by third-party advertisers appear on Weekly Women when you visit the site. These companies may use information about your visits, not including your name, address or email address or telephone number, to be able to serve you with the most interesting advertisements. Click here for more information about the advertising process, including not having your information used by these third-party advertisers.

**Links on Weekly Women**

Weekly Women is not responsible for privacy practices of third-party websites that are unaffiliated with us, even though Weekly Women may contain links to these sites. Weekly Women will not sure your personal information with them. Please make sure you read the privacy policies of these third-party websites.

**How Weekly Women Controls Your Personal Data**

Personal information included with your submissions may allow third parties to identify and associate you with your user account or even contact you. Please keep any private information out of your submissions.

By reading this, you are releasing Weekly Women from any and all claims that arise from or are related to unauthorized use of information that is intercepted while being sent via the internet and acknowledging that Weekly Women is not responsible for intercepted information.

**Changes and Terms to the Privacy Policy**

At any time, modifications may be made to this privacy policy, with updates being posted to this page. If changes to how your personal information is used are made, Weekly Women will notify you via email to the latest address you provided and/or by posting a notice prominently on our website. These changes will take effect 30 calendar days following the email or posting on our website, whichever is earlier.

**Contacting us and Access to Personal Information**

If you have questions regarding anything listed in the privacy policy, privacy practices of Weekly Women or to utilize the rights granted here, please use the contact form to contact us. Through a written request, Weekly Women will discuss the disclosure and use, as well as grant access to your personal information.
